# ARTUR BAGDASARIANI

# **SUMMARY**

Strong knowledge of C# fundamentals and OOP principles, HTML, CSS, Javascript. Seeking an entry level web developer position. Previously, almost two year practical experience gained in financial industries, in top audit firms. Expertise in preparing financial statements and conducting ratio analysis of real-world businesses.

## SKILLS

PROGRAMMING: HTML, CSS, Javascript, C#, Python

SOFTWARE: ERP systems, Microsoft Office

LANGUAGES: Georgian, Russian, English, Armenian, Chinese

## **COURSES**

#### Responsive Web Design Certification - freeCodeCamp

Sept. 2020 - Oct. 2020

Learnt basic HTML, CSS and responsive web design principles

# The Web Developer Bootcamp - Udemy

Sept. 2020 - Current

Learning fundamentals of web development, in particular advanced HTML, CSS, Javascript

## ASP.NET Core Developer - ITVDN

Aug. 2020 - Current

Learning C# fundamentals, object-oriented programming principles

# **PROJECTS**

#### **Survey form ♂**

Responsive web page, where user should fill survey

#### To-do list ┌↗

To-do list with quite nice interface using JavaScript and jQuery

#### 

A responsive one-page website with modern design for travel agency

#### Calculator 7

Windows forms application written on C#

#### 

Game where user should memorize allocation of same picture in order to win

# **EMPLOYMENT**

# KPMG, Auditor, Tbilisi, Georgia

Aug. 2019 - Oct. 2020

• Performed audit procedures during projects within different teams. Industry background: banking, retailing, mining, realestate etc.

## Grant Thornton, Business Process Analyst, Tbilisi, Georgia

Mar. 2019 - July 2019

• Performed outsourcing of financial accounting services to firms specializing in logistics, hospitality and IT industries

## **EDUCATION**

#### **International Black Sea University**

2016 - 2020

Bachelor of Business and Technologies GPA 93%

# SolBridge International School of Business

2017 - 2018

Exchange program in South Korea

## AWARDS

Silver Medal, Ministry of Education and Science of Georgia

June 2016